creativityworks.eu 2019-05-10

# CW! Privacy Policy - Creativity Works

We respect the privacy of every person who visits or registers with creativityworks.eu (the “Site”) and we are committed to ensuring a safe online experience.

##### 1\. Purpose of this Policy

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains our approach to any personal information that we might collect from you and the purposes for which we process your personal information. This Privacy Policy also sets out your rights in respect of our processing of your personal information. It is designed to be in compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

This Privacy Policy will inform you of the nature of the personal information about you that is processed by us and how you can request that we delete, update, transfer it and/or provide you with access to it. This Privacy Policy is intended to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Site

We may change this policy by updating this page. Please check regularly to be informed of any modifications.

##### 2\. Who are we and what do we do?

Creativity Works! is a coalition of organisations, federations and associations representing Europe’s cultural and creative sectors. Our diverse membership includes writers, screenwriters, book publishers and retailers, picture agencies, music publishers, independent music labels, producers, publishers and distributors of film and audiovisual content, cinema operators, broadcasters, sports event organisers, as well as video game developers and publishers.

The Site and our Services are operated by G Plus Limited and G Plus Europe Limited (“We”). We are a limited company. Our main trading address is 42 Rue Breydel, 1040 Brussels, Belgium.

##### 3\. How to contact us?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or want to exercise your rights set out in this Privacy Policy, please contact us by:

– sending an e-mail to info@creativityworks.eu  
– or write to us at rue Breydel 42, 1040 Brussels. 

##### 4\. What personal information do we collect and how do we use it? 

On our website, we list our contact details. In the case we receive an inquiry, we use the contact details you have provided to us to maintain contact with you and respond to your request.

Such processing is based on our legitimate interest to conduct our work and we store your information only for a time period and/or as it is necessary for the above mentioned purposes.

The data that we hold will not be shared with any third parties for marketing purposes. We may use third-party service providers to perform operations on our behalf like sending postal mail and e-mails. They are compliant with the GDPR and may not use the shared data for other purposes. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. Any security issues will be communicated to you.

##### 5\. Our use of cookies 

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our Site. 

We use the following cookies: analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. By using this information, we are able to measure the effectiveness of our content and how visitors use our Site. This allows us to learn what pages of our Site are most attractive to our visitors, and which parts of our Site are the most interesting.

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them below:  
– Cookie: Google Analytics  
– Name: _utma _utmb _utmc _utmz

– Purpose: These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.

**How to refuse cookies**

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  
– In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.  
– In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”.  
– In Chrome, go to ‘Tools Menu’, ‘Options’, ‘Under the Hood’, ‘Cookie Setting’ and select ‘Block all Cookies’

You may also choose to install [Google Analytics’ opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

All analytics cookies will expire within 2 years from their last use. For more information, read [Google Analytics cookie usage info](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage#gajs) .

##### 6\. Third Party Links 

Our Site could contain links to third party websites. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another website, this Privacy Policy no longer applies.

Your browsing and interaction on any other websites is subject to that website’s or third party service provider’s own rules and policies. We do not monitor, control, or endorse the privacy practices of any third parties. We encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of every website you visit or third party service provider that you deal with and to contact them if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies and practices.

This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by us through our Service and does not apply to other third party websites and third party service providers.

##### 7\. Confidentiality and security of your personal information

We are committed to keeping the personal information you provide to us secure and we will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration, and in no case less precautions than for our own sensitive data.

##### 8\. How to access your information and your other rights?

In compliance with the conditions set out in the GDPR, you have the following rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you: right of access, right to rectification, right to erasure, right to restrict processing, right to data portability, right to object, rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling, right to withdraw consent, and right to lodge a complaint with the Belgian supervisory authority (currently, the [Commission for the protection of privacy](https://www.privacycommission.be/en)).

In such cases, please email us at [info@creativityworks.eu](mailto:info@creativityworks.eu) or write to us at rue Breydel 42, 1040 Brussels.

##### 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

To ensure that you are always aware of how we use your personal information we will update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect any changes to our use of your personal information. We may also make changes as required to comply with changes in applicable law or regulatory requirements. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be informed of how we use your personal information.
